<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>ST科技战斗包 - Technology Battle Pack (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.STTechnologyBattlePack</packageId>
  <author>FD.FLY;LingLuo</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/STTechnologyBattlePack</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of FD.FLY;LingLuos mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=863786159

Machine translation: 
A collection of the latest black technologies in the ST zone, including:
1. Group position, used as a belt, active activation, consumption of energy to provide protection or abnormal status for surrounding friendly or enemy forces
2. The group shield, used as a belt, is automatically opened to protect the friendly forces around the character
3. Grenade belt, used as a belt, actively used, allowing you to use the grenade while using the gun, which truly restores the accuracy of the grenade
4. The vortex shield, used as a shield, is passively activated to reflect the enemy's bullets back, but note that the smarter the character, the more accurately the bullet can be reflected to the enemy
5. Energy shield, used as a shield, passively opened, can resist melee shields, while allowing you to use long-range weapons
6. Shooting elves, used as a belt, passively turned on, the elves will copy your bullets when you shoot, and double your firepower

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/STTechnologyBattlePack][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
ST星区最新黑科技的集合，包含：
1.群体立场，作为挂件使用，主动开启，消耗充能为周围友军或敌军提供加护或异常状态
2.群体护盾，作为挂件使用，主动开启，庇护人物周围的友军
3.手雷腰带，作为挂件使用，主动使用，让你在使用枪的同时，使用手雷,真实的还原了手雷的精度
4.漩涡护盾，作为护盾使用，被动开启，将敌人的子弹反射回去，但注意，人物越聪明，越能将子弹准确的反射到敌人身上
5.能量护盾，作为护盾使用，被动开启，可以抵抗近战的护盾，同时让你可以使用远程武器
6.射击精灵，作为挂件使用，被动开启，精灵会在你射击的时复制你的弹，让你的火力加倍
request for english translate

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]</description>
</ModMetaData>